Just another day in the neighbourhood.
又到了开工的日子了
Keep firing!
继续开火!
It didn't have to go like this.
非得这么做不成吗
Yates, don't just sit there, return fire! Let's go!
Yates 别坐在那儿发呆 回击啊! 咱们走!
Angel! He's hit Russell.
Angel! 他打中了Russell
Son of a bitch. Why the hell weren't you covering him?
狗娘养的 你他妈的为什么没有掩护他?
- You're good, okay. - Yates...Yates,cover me.
- 你会没事的 - 掩护我
YEAH
嗯
He's down! He's down!
他倒下了! 他倒下了!
Stay here.
待在这儿
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 玩火 第一季第9集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 玩火 第一季第9集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：面瘫君
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：瑜香 校对：酒囊饭袋 时间轴：面瘫君
You know this thing is amazing. I can push my ISO like crazy.
这东西真是棒极了 我可以感光度调到最高
- I could shoot in a closet and there would be zero noise. - Come on.
- 我可以躲在柜子里偷拍 然后完全没有噪点 - 好了啦
You should let me take your picture, you're a beautiful man.
你应该让我多给你拍拍照的 你长的这么帅
I do let you; that one time in Mexico wearing the sombrero.
我让你拍啦 那次在墨西哥 戴着宽边帽拍的
- Yeah and you were drunk and mooning me. - Go to work.
- 是啊 当时你喝醉了 我俩在一起闲逛 - 去上班吧
OKAY , COME HERE
好 过来亲亲
WHAT....
怎么啦?
You're scared the camera's gonna reveal your deep dark secrets to me. Am I right?
你是不是害怕镜头会揭发出 你那些见不得光的秘密 我说得对吗
What happens if you find out what a terrible person I am?
万一被你发现我是个很可怕的人怎么办?
I'll take my chances. Bye.
我愿意冒险一试 拜拜
See you tonight.
今晚见
The SMASH unit. Guns and Gangs.
SMASH组 扫黑缉枪科的
We think there could be a coverup. SMASH guys initiated the shoot out.
我们认为可能有事被隐瞒了 SMASH的人先开的枪
We're not convinced they had cause. We've been concerned with this unit for some time.
我们不确定他们有正当理由 我们担心这个组有一段时间了
- Their tactics, their use of force. - So why haven't you pulled them from duty?
- 他们的战术 对于武力的使用 - 那你为什么不叫停他们?
We haven't been able to prove anything. That's where you come in.
我们还没能证明什么 所以这才需要你们
This guy was a veteran banger, Eight convictions. Trafficking, aggravated assault.
这家伙是个经验丰富的硬汉 八次定罪 毒品交易 故意伤害
Wait a second, you're actually going to go after the SMASH unit?
等等 你们真的要查SMASH组?
You think that's wise? These guys are decorated cops.
你觉得这样明智吗 这些家伙可是战功累累
- They're pretty much rock stars. - Then I'm sure you won't find anything.
- 他们是警察中的明星 - 那么我很确定你不会查到什么
And if we do? They're also well connected.
那万一查出来了呢 他们的人脉肯定也很广
The CIU is still a new unit, this could finish us.
我们还是一个新的部门 这事儿会让我们完蛋的
An assignment like this is why you're in the budget. It isn't up for debate, Rebecca.
之所以给你们拨款 就是为了处理这样的事务的 这事儿没什么可商量的 Rebecca
If you think these guys aren't lying, then prove it.
如果你觉得这些人没有在说谎 那就想办法证明
That's Daniel's old unit, you know that right?
那是Daniel以前的部门 你知道的对吧?
You're serious? We're working with Internal Affairs?
你是认真的? 我们要跟内务部合作?
Isn't there like a rule about looking into other cops?
不是说有一个规矩嘛 关于调查其他警察的?
- Yeah,the rule is that you don't do it. - You don't even think about it.
- 规矩就是别这么做 - 连想都不要去想
Daniel, you ran with these guys. You want to set it up?
Daniel你跟这些家伙们共事过 要不你来介绍一下?
The SMASH unit. Some of the best cops I've worked with.
SMASH组 跟我合作过的警察中最优秀的一批人
They pound the streets. They make a ton of arrests.
他们四处出击 抓过的坏人不计其数
Sometimes they get a little cowboy, not everyone understands that.
有时候他们会表现得有点出格 这一点并不是每个人都能理解
Especially Internal Affairs.
尤其是内务部
Angel Abano, one of their guys.
Angel Abano 他们中的一员
He was injured during the shoot out. They need someone to take his place.
在火拼中受伤 他们需要找人来接替他的位子
That's going to be Jesse. He's new, they won't know him.
所以就是Jesse了 他是新人 他们不会认识他
Daniel, I'm going to list you as a reference on Jesse's paperwork I need you to set it up.
Daniel 我会把你作为推荐人 就在你要为Jesse准备的的档案里
- What if I refuse? - Then you can give me a call from traffic duty,
- 万一我拒绝这么做呢 - 那你不如去当交警吧
remind me how itchy that poly blend is in 80 degree heat.
到时候记得跟我说说大热天 穿着那身化纤制服浑身有多痒痒
- ??? - No!
- 别 Rebecca 别这样 - 不行
None of you get to act like you're any more upset about this than I am. Our job is to find out the truth.
你们都别弄得好像比我还生气的样子 我们的工作是找出真相
Are they lying about the shooting? If so, what really happened out there?
关于火拼他们是不是撒谎了? 如果是的话 那么到底发生了什么?
If they're clean, we prove it and IA steps down.
如果他们是清白的 我们提供证明 内务部就会知难而退了
We treat this like any other case.
我们要像对待其他任何案子一样
Jesse.
Jesse
Alright, listen up.
好了 听着
Russell Hagler, he runs the unit.
Russell Hagler 那是部门的头头
He's the one you need to impress, he's the key to this whole thing.
你需要给他留下好印象 他是一切的关键
You two were close?
你们俩关系很铁?
YEAH.
是的
Russell was my mentor, three years.
Russell以前是我的导师 三年
He's like a big brother.
他就像个大哥哥
- What about that guy? -That's Russell's right-hand man; Kevin Yates.
- 那么那个人呢 - 那是Russell的左膀右臂 Kevin Yates
He's a good guy, real police.
他是个好人 真正的警察
Alright, let's go tell Rebecca you're ready.
好了 走吧 告诉Rebecca你准备好了
Daniel will set up the first introduction.
Daniel会给你引荐
The SMASH guys always drink at the same bar; we'll do it on their home turf.
SMASH的人总是在同一家酒吧喝酒 我们就从他们的老巢开始
Jesse needs to make a good first impression, his entry into the unit depends on it.
Jesse得留下一个不错的第一印象 他能不能进这个部门就靠这个了
Daniel will run cover. I want everyone on their A game.
Daniel负责掩护 我要每个人 都打起十二万分的精神来
The faster we move, the faster we can close the book on this.
我们行动越迅速 就能越快把这案子了了
Yeah, tequila!
龙舌兰!
I keep thinking, we're cops, we're supposed to protect each other.
我一直在想 我们是警察 我们应该互相保护的
Yeah, you keep thinking that.
没错 你继续这么想吧
Look, at some point, they're going to test you, okay?
听着 在某个时刻 他们会给你个测试 明白吗
It's an initiation. Just roll with it, okay?
表示着你的加入 你该怎么做就怎么做 明白吗
What about you. You up for this?
那你呢 你也做过吗
Hell yeah, time of my damn life.
没错 那是我生命中的一段美好时光
- The prodigal son returns. - I knew I smelled something when I walked in here.
- 浪子回头了哈 - 我走进来的时候就闻到了你们的气味
You still got that halitosis problem, eh Pounds?
你那口臭的毛病还是没好 对吧?
Why don't you gimme a kiss, and you'll find out.
不如咱俩亲一下 你就会知道了
Sure tonight's not gonna be too much action for you?
你确定今晚没什么活要干嘛?
Hope you're up for some drinking, my friend.
来一起喝两杯吧 我的朋友
Here he is, Jesse Borden, straight out of OPC.
这位就是了 Jesse Borden 刚从警校毕业的
Hotshot of his class. The academy's best kept secret.
班上的牛人 最优秀的学员
Is that so? Doesn't explain why you wanna be in my unit.
是嘛? 但这也不能说明 你为什么想要加入我的部门啊
Ever since I was a kid. I wanted to help people.
当我还是个孩子时 我就想要帮助人们
Protect them.
保护他们
Well, no offense kid, but we chase street waste.
好吧 不是想吓唬你 孩子 但是我们要对付的可是街头恶霸
- You wanna save people, go be a nurse. - Hey,come on, man, you gotta settle down.
- 如果你想要救死扶伤的话 不如去当护士 - 嗨 悠着点儿
You're gonna scare the kid off before we even started.
咱们还没开始呢 你就要把这孩子吓尿了
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU. You look good, Danny Boy. C'mon, I'll buy you a drink.
你看上去气色不错 小Danny 来吧 我请你喝一杯
THANKS MAN
谢了 兄弟
- You gonna sit down? - How's Terri?
- 坐下来说嘛? - Terri最近怎么样?
O, COME ON MAN. You haven't seen me since I took homicide,
自从我去了凶杀组咱俩就没见过了
and you automatically think I'm with the same woman?
然后你想当然的以为我还没换女朋友?
We're getting married this winter.
今年冬天我们就要结婚了
Same old Danny Price. Most loyal guy I've ever known.
Danny Price果然一点都没变 是我认识的最忠诚的人
Hey look man, how's Angel?
Angel怎么样了?
He's doing alright, he's tough.
他还可以 他很坚强
- You hear Yates is retiring? - Yeah?
- 你听说Yates要退休了嘛? - 是嘛?
He's getting old and soft. I need somebody young.
他老了 也开始手软了 所以我需要年轻人
This Jesse kid looks straight laced.
这个叫Jesse的小子看着有点儿娘啊
- YEAH - Is he going to fit in?
他干这个合适吗
YEAH, He's good, scrappy. I know his brother.
他很不错 挺好斗的 我认识他哥哥
Don't let the pretty boy routine fool you. He's a tough kid.
别被他的外表骗了 他是个很坚强的孩子
Drink up, Jesse, they're on the house.
喝吧 Jesse 免费的
They know we're cops?
他们知道我们是警察?
Kid, everybody here knows who we are.
孩子 这里所有的人都知道我们是谁
We'll set up a cover apartment for Jesse. It'll be fully wired.
我们会给Jesse准备一间掩护公寓 公寓会被全面监听
Khali will set up cameras and mics. Full coverage.
Khali会设置好摄像头和麦克风 全覆盖
There's something going on with Yates. He's hiding something.
Yates有事 他在隐藏些什么
- I got a hit off him. - Look,you're the new guy on the team.
- 我能感觉到他的不对劲 - 你是团队里的新人
- They're going to be watching you, all of them. - I don't know,
- 他们会盯着你的 所有的人 - 我也不知道为什么
Yates felt different, he's more intense.
但是Yates给人感觉不一样 他好像更紧张
ALLRIGHT, Then you keep an eye on him, alright? Don't make up stories.
- 那你就盯着他点儿 好嘛 - 不要编故事
Hey, come here.
嗨 过来一下
I want you to go easyon him. If he tells you he got a hit, you listen.
我要你对他客气一点儿 如果他告诉你感觉到了什么 你就听他说
- LOOK, I don't need a pep talk right now. - Is there something you're not telling me?
- 现在我不需要你给我打气 - 你是不是有什么事情没告诉我的?
It's business. Let's just do the job.
这是公事 咱们公事公办
Get some sleep.
睡一觉
- How you doing? - I've been better.
- 你还好吗 - 比之前好点了
I've got cameras and mics in place. They'll be up by tomorrow.
我把摄像头和麦克风都设置好了 明天早上就会启动
- Full coverage, everything except... - Except bedroom?
- 全面覆盖 除了... - 除了卧室?
Good night, Jesse.
晚安 Jesse
I miss you.
我想你
You need to sleep.
你该睡觉了
And I need to get out of here before I do something stupid.So...
而我得在做出什么蠢事之前离开这儿 所以...
Talk to you later, okay?
晚点再聊 好嘛?
Khali.
Khali
- You feel like taking a ride? - Hey, what's going on?
- 想出去转转吗 - 嗨 怎么了?
We working tonight?
我们今晚有行动?
Hey, what are you doing?
嗨 你这是干什么?
This won't hurt a bit.
不会弄疼你的
Don't move until I tell you.
让你动 你再动
So, think you can just show up out of nowhere and join my unit?
你觉得自己可以从石头缝里蹦出来 然后就能加入我的部门?
This is the real deal, kid. You got what it takes to be here?
咱们可是动真格的 孩子 你有足够的能力加入么?
- Yeah.I think so. - No, you either do or you don't!
- 我想是的 - 不 你要么能 要么不能!
Screw you.
去死吧你
Good. That's more like it.
很好 这个回答还靠谱一些
NOW...There are three kilos of H inside that house, maybe more.
房子里有3公斤的海洛因 或者更多
You're going to go in there and get it for me.
你进去里面 拿到东西来给我
- What about a warrant? - Don't worry about that, we've got it covered.
- 那搜查令呢 - 不用担心那个 我们已经搞定了
Move!
行动!
You want to run with SMASH, learn to improvise.
你想要在SMASH干活 就得学会即兴发挥
Now go.
去吧
?????????
即兴
Police! Don't move!
警察! 不许动!
- We have a warrant to search the premises. PUT THE WEAPON DOWN - You can't just come into my house.
- 我们对这座房屋有搜查令 放下武器 - 你不能就这样闯进我家
C'mon, Andre, be a good boy; Tell us where the drugs are.
得了吧 Andre 做个乖孩子 告诉我们毒品在哪里
Screw you man, not till I see your warrant.
去你的吧 除非让我见到搜查令
You wanna see my warrant, Andre?
你想要看看我的搜查令 Andre?
Let's just see if I can find my warrant, huh.
让我来看看我能不能找到它
Nope. Not here.
没有 不在这儿
Hey, hey! Don't touch that.
嗨 嗨! 别碰那个
THAT was my mom's stuff.
那是我妈妈的东西
NO
不要啊
What do you think, Russell? Should I leave this stuff alone?
你觉得呢 Russell? 我该放下这东西吗
You know what we came for.
你知道我们的来意的
Uhh-uhh. All right.
- 别动 - 好吧
Come on, Andre, where are the drugs?
说吧 Andre 毒品在哪儿?
- THAT'S ENOUGH - COME ON
- 够了 - 说啊
No, no, no. Leave that alone, don't touch it.
不 不 不 把那个放下 别碰它
What are you doing man? You said this was your mom's stuff.
- 你在干什么? - 你说这以前是你妈妈的东西
- This must be your mom, then. - Put that down.
- 那么这个估计就是你妈本人了 - 把它放下
- Put it down. - I'll put it right over here.
- 放下 - 我就把它放在这儿
How far down you think this thing goes, Andre?
你觉得这东西能掉到多深的地方 Andre?
- You wanna take a guess? - C'mon, where's the drugs?
你想要猜猜看吗 得了吧 东西在哪里?
You better tell him, Andre.
你最好告诉他 Andre
Stop!
住手!
- There she goes. - No!
- 她走咯 - 不要!
Be smart. We're not leaving without the stuff.
学聪明点 东西不到手我们是不会走的
It's up to you how hard you wanna make this.
事情会变的有多难看 完全取决于你
Okay, you're the boss.
好了 现在你是老板
Okay! Okay! Okay!
好了! 好了! 好了!
I'll tell you. Just stop!
我告诉你 你住手!
- What? - It's in the air conditioner out back. All of it.
- 在哪儿? - 在后面的空调里 都在里面了
Give me that.
给我
HA HA, Mama's boy.
哈哈 妈妈的乖孩子
You're sick, kid, you know that, right?
你很牛 孩子 你知道的 对么?
And you, you're getting off lucky.
还有你 今晚算你走运
Yates, you found us.
Yates 你找到我们了
I thought we weren't doing this tonight.
我以为今晚咱们不会开工的
Yeah well, I guess I forgot to call you.
哦 那个啊 我想我是忘了打电话给你了
What went on here tonight, you like it?
今晚发生的这些事 你喜欢吗
Is that your style?
是你喜欢的风格吗
- I was just doing my job, man. - Yeah?
- 我只是在做我的工作 老兄 - 是嘛?
It only gets worse from here.
从今以后只会每况愈下
You better get ready.
你最好有心理准备
So last night, SMASH unit broke into a civilian's house, trashed it, and threatened him with violence.
所以昨晚 SMASH闯入并砸烂了一个平民的家 并用暴力威胁了他
They didn't lay a single charge.
他们没有提出任何控罪
LOOK, I don't know it would get out of hand like that.
听着 我不知道事情会变成那样
- He was trying to impress Russell, and it worked. - It was an initiation and Jesse passed, with flying colors.
- 他只是想要给Russell留下个好印象 而且成功了 - 那是个入门考验 Jesse通过了 而且是高分过关
What happened last night was good. He's in.
昨晚发生的事很不错 他入伙了
We're trying to prove the unit's doing things by the book. If last night's any indication...
我们还得证明他们是按照规矩行事的 如果昨晚的事是个迹象的话...
Last night doesn't prove anything.
昨晚的事不能证明任何东西
Sometimes you gotta bend the rules. These guys know that.
有时候你会逾矩行事 这些人很清楚这一点
You're telling me you would go into someone's house, damage their property, threaten them.
你是说你会闯入某人的家 破坏他们的财产 威胁他们
Yes I would, if I had to.
是的 我会 如果我必须这么做的话
Three kilos of heroin went into lock up early this morning, care of SMASH unit.
今天早上SMASH上缴了3公斤的海洛因
Silver lining?
柳暗花明又一村?
The second in command, Yates. He wasn't there for the raid.
那个副手 Yates 他没有参加昨晚的突袭
- Showed up later. - You said there was tension?
- 他很晚才现身的 - 你说当时有紧张的气氛?
- Big time. - All right.
- 非常 - 好吧
That's a crack. If they're on the outs, Russell's going to be looking for allies.
说明他们有了嫌隙 如果他们意见不合 Russell应该会寻找支持他的人
I want you to stay close, show him you're going to be loyal.
我要你紧跟着他们 让他知道你会忠于他
Hey, there's no reason to let IA know about last night's stunt. Right?
嗨 我觉得不必让内务部知道昨晚的事
- Don't tell me you're not concerned? - The SMASH unit they know the law.
- 你别告诉我你毫不担心? - SMASH知道法律是如何规定的
They play in the grey when they need to. I've seen you bend rules before Rebecca.
他们游走在灰色地带 我也曾经见过你违反规定行事的 Rebacca
Don't give me the brotherhood speech. I'm a cop, I know what it means to protect each other.
你少跟我来这种所谓的兄弟间的谈话 我也是个警察 我知道互相保护是什么意思
And here comes the "But".
然后你会说"但是"
If this is how these guys operate, you don't think they'd cover up an illegal shooting?
如果这些家伙是像这样干活的 你不认为他们会掩盖一场非法的火拼么?
You're part of a murder now, you know.
你现在是谋杀的一部分了 你知道的
You passed the test.
你通过了测试
What are you talking about a "murder"?
你说"谋杀"是什么意思?
You know everybody thinks eagles are baddass 'cause they fly alone,
你知道大家都觉得老鹰不是什么好东西 因为它们总是独自行动
but they got nothing on crows.
但是它们跟乌鸦没法比
You fly alone, you get yourself killed.
你独自行动 就是将自己置于死地
OKAY, The unit, is like a murder of crows.
这个部门 就像是一群杀人的乌鸦
Crows'll gather to decide the capital fate of another. Make their own laws.
乌鸦们聚集在一起 决定另外一个人的命运 自己制定规则
We're in a war against the streets, we can't win, Jesse.
我们是在跟街头霸王们开战 我们赢不了的 Jesse
You gotta choose which side of the battle you're on.
你得选好自己在战斗中站在哪一边
Here, double cream, double sugar.
给你 要双份的奶油和糖
Hey! Police don't move!
警察! 不许动!
You don't know what you're doing, man. It looks like I got you on unlawful possession.
- 你不知道自己在干什么 伙计 - 看上去我可以以非法持有毒品的罪名来抓你
You don't want to do that.
你不想这么做的
And what's this? Possession for the purposes of.
还有这是什么? 持有并意图贩卖
Jesse, you've gotta stop.
Jesse 你得住手
- Let him go. - Are you serious?
- 让他走 - 你是认真的?
He's got like 3 grams here; I just found a .38 in his underwear.
他身上至少有3克 裤子里还藏着一把点38
That little bit? Time we spend processing this guy.
就这么点? 为了这点东西花时间处置他不值得
You wanna tell me what the hell's going on with Russell IH THERE?
你能告诉我Russell他妈的在干嘛吗
YEAH, I'd like to coach, but I'm pretty much in the dark myself.
我也想教教你 但我本人也被蒙在鼓里
Get in the car.
进车里去
- Don't move. - Wait a second.
- 别动 - 等等
You see this? He just gave him his gun back.
你看到了吗 他把枪还给他了
I'm bringing the kid in. You stay with Jesse.
我把那小孩带回去 你跟着Jesse
Lucas Smith, AKA Baby Luke.
Lucas Smith 江湖人称Baby Luke
Did a stint in juvie, no arrests in 3 years. Known member of the Marvo Crew.
在少管所待过 最近3年没有逮捕记录 是Marvo帮的成员
Which is the biggest gang in the SMASH unit's jurisdiction.
是SMASH辖区内最大的黑帮
If they're so big how come there are hardly any arrests in here?
如果他们的组织如此壮大 怎么可能一起逮捕都没有?
The Marvo Crew run a pretty good racket
Marvo帮玩得很开
Must be nice to move all that dope, while SMASH unit looks the other way.
能把那些毒品都处理掉一定很厉害 与此同时SMASH假装没看见
- How much you pay them? - SMASH, what's SMASH?
- 你们付给他们多少钱? - SMASH 什么是SMASH?
I don't know what you're talking about, lady.
我不知道你在说什么 女士
No? Then why did they let you walk when they found drugs and a gun on you today?
不知道? 那今天他们为什么在发现你 携带毒品和枪支之后还让你走了?
- Didn't let me walk far, I'm in here aren't I? - It was my people who brought you in, not SMASH.
- 也没让我走太远 我现在不正在这儿嘛 - 是我的人带你来的 不是SMASH
- C'mon, Luke, how much are you paying those cops? - It's got to be enough to make it worth their while, right?
- 说吧 Luke 你付给那些警察多少钱? - 肯定足够让他们高抬贵手了 对吗
I've got nothing to say to you so why don't you run and get my lawyer now?
我没什么要说的 不如你帮我把我的律师找来吧?
See, that's the good news. You don't need a lawyer.
听着 好消息是 你不需要律师
We're going to let you go.
我们会放你走
But first we're gonna put a call into the SMASH guys and tell them what you said.
但是首先我们会给SMASH的人打电话 告诉他们你说了什么
How you told us all about them. How they're taking bribes, how they're dirty...
你是如何把他们都交待出来的 他们是如何收取贿赂的 他们是怎么做坏事...
Whoa, whoa, I didn't say any of that.
我可什么都没说啊
Okay. We'll just sit back and watch.
好的 我们只要坐等好戏开场就行了
You don't have to rat them out. We just wait to see what they do to you.
你不必出卖他们 我们只需要等着 看他们会对你做什么
And that will be our evidence, right?
然后那就会成为我们的证据 对嘛?
All right look, I'll take the charge, plead guilty, whatever you want. All right just...
好了 听着 你们可以告我 我接受辩诉交易 无论你们要什么都行 只要...
please, don't do this.
拜托了 别这么做
You're really that afraid of them? You need to tell me why.
你真的就那么怕他们? 你得告诉我为什么
I'll get someone to escort you out of here. Come on.
我会找人护送你出去的 走吧
Let me go! Wait. Alright!
放开我! 等等 好吧!
You put it out there I'm a rat they're both gonna want me dead.
你放我出去 我就会变成过街老鼠 两边都会要了我的命的
Both?
两边?
- What's that supposed to mean? - Don't you get it?
- 这是什么意思? - 你还不明白吗
They're working together. Those cops and the Marvo Crew, they partnered up.
他们是一伙的 那些警察和Marvo帮 他们是合作关系
They're working the hood together.
他们玩转这一带
SMASH is running the whole show.
SMASH操作了整件事
Alright, sit down.
好了 坐下
Stick with me, Jesse, I'll take care of you.
紧跟着我 Jesse 我会照顾你的
I can be your best friend, don't forget that.
我可以成为你最好的朋友 别忘了这一点
See these guys, M3 Colts. Used to run this neighborhood,
看到那些家伙了吗 是M3 Colts的人 以前掌控这个街区
before we came in and cleaned it up.
直到我们来这儿 把他们清扫出去
Wanna make an arrest so badly? Let's make one.
你很想抓坏人不是吗 咱们就抓一个
We're good here, Russell, it's fine. These guys are clean.
这里没事 Russell 没问题 这些家伙是清白的
Doesn't look fine to me.
我不觉得他们没问题
Jesse, check the backseat, tell me what you see.
Jesse 查查后座 告诉我有什么发现
What are you doing, Russell?
你这是在干什么 Russell?
- Nothing in there.
- 什么也没有
Really?
是嘛?
Really now, Russell.
你不是吧 Russell
What's this?
这是什么?
Congrats, kid. You get to make your first arrest.
恭喜你 孩子 你的第一次逮捕来了
I was pissed enough that Internal Affairs was poking around,
内务部到处管闲事已经够让我火大的了
- then I get your call. - Sir.
- 然后我还接到了你的电话 - 长官
- Do you have any idea... - The shooting wasn't clean, sir.
- 你知不知道... - 那次交火是另有隐情的 长官
The SMASH unit is allied with a gang, the Marvo Crew.
SMASH在跟一个黑帮合作 Marvo帮
- They shot that kid over turf. - You know this, how?
- 他们因为争夺地盘才射杀了那个孩子 - 你是怎么知道的?
Some scumbag drug dealer told you? I mean the kid's looking for a deal, Rebecca.
某个混蛋毒贩子告诉你的? 这孩子是想做以此来做交易 Rebecca
Accusing four cops is a suicide play, not a deal.
指控四名警察无异于自掘坟墓 不是什么交易
My guys witnessed Russell Hagler returning a weapon to a gang member.
我的人亲眼见到了Russell Hagler 把一支武器交还给帮派成员
I could arrest him right now.
我现在就可以抓他的
- Look, I hate this as much as you do. - You want to hand this off to me, is that why you called?
- 听着 我和你一样痛恨这种事 - 你想把这个烫手山芋丢给我 所以才打电话给我?
No sir, I want to pursue it.
不 长官 我想要追查到底
If we don't, we're choosing to look the other way. There's a point where the brotherhood ends.
如果我们不查 我们就会选择视而不见 总有那么一个点 兄弟之情分崩离析的
- The information you've come across could be nothing. - It isn't.
- 你所得到的信息可能没有任何价值 - 不是这样的
Whatever your guys think they saw... we don't know what that was.
不管你的人看到了什么... 我们不知道背后到底是什么
- So you're planning to bury this? - Hey, careful.
- 所以你是打算把这件事盖过去? - 说话注意点
If you pursue this, and you're wrong? You'll go down, hard.
如果你追查下去 然后发现自己错了呢 你就会一落千丈 狠狠地摔在地上
This unit, your career, whatever you thought you knew, will be gone.
这个部门 你的前途 不管你认为你认识谁 都会烟消云散的
Due respect, sir, you need to start thinking about what could happen if I'm right.
恕我直言 长官 你得开始想想 万一我是对的会发生些什么
If you're right, I'll protect you.
如果你是对的 我会保护你
But so far, Detective Sergeant? I'm unconvinced.
但是到目前为止 探长 我表示怀疑
You think that kid Luke's telling the truth?
你觉得那个叫Luke的小子说的是实话?
SMASH is working with the Marvos.
SMASH在跟Marvo帮合作
Looks that way, yeah.
看上去是的
I want everyone in briefing, now.
叫所有人一起来开会 马上
You need to think about your reputation, your future as cops.
你得考虑自己的声誉 作为警察的前途
It's your decision.
决定权在你们自己手上
If you go after other police, that's going to stick.
如果你要查的是其他的警察 那你就得坚持到底
So this Luke kid, his word is iron clad?
所以这个叫Luke的小子 他说的话就是铁板一块?
Daniel, you watched Russell hand that weapon back to that kid yourself.
Daniel 你亲眼看到Russell把那把枪还给那小子的
- Jesse saw him planting drugs. - So why aren't we picking him up?
- Jesse看到他把毒品栽赃给别人 - 那为什么我们现在不去抓他?
Because I want them all. The entire unit.
因为我想要一网打尽 整个部门
I'm not ordering you to do this. It's up to you.
我不是在命令你们去做 做不做由你们自己决定
From this point on,
从现在起
if you move forward with this operation it's because you chose to.
如果你参加了这次行动 那是因为你自己选择了要参加的
- Alright, so we're with you. - Okay.
- 好 我们都跟你 - 好的
- We believe that SMASH is in bed with The Marvo Crew. - According to Luke, the Marvos get a free pass.
我们认为SMASH跟Marvo帮是一伙的 据Luke所说 Marvos有通行证
Their rivals, the M3 Colts, get nailed every time.
而他们的对头 M3 Colts 每次都会被抓
Part of what they seize, they re-sell on the streets.
他们拿到的其中一部分 会重新拿回去出售
- The rest goes into lock up. - That's a lot of drug money.
- 剩下的会被上缴 - 那可是一大笔钱啊
So what about Yates? He's unhappy.
那么Yates呢 他不太高兴
- He's already leaving the unit. - Could mean he's ready to flip.
- 他已经要离开这个部门了 - 也许意味着他准备揭发他们了
We need to reach out to him.
我们需要找他谈谈
Russell's all over me. I can't get near Yates.
Russell整天盯着我 我没办法接近Yates
What if I can?
那如果我能呢
Look, this is my unit, not SMASH.
听着 这里才是我的部门 不是SMASH
Let's do this.
咱们行动吧
I thought only girls smoked those.
我还以为只有女孩子才抽那种烟呢
You're just jealous 'cause I make these look good.
你这纯粹是出于妒忌 因为我抽烟的样子很酷
Yeah you keep telling yourself that. What's going on?
你就继续自欺欺人吧 你怎么样?
You seen Jesse? I tried calling him.
你见到Jesse了吗 我给他打电话一直联系不上
YEAH, He's with Russell, we got squad soon.
他跟Russell在一块儿 我们马上就要成为五人组了
No. You should go easy, you got shift soon.
不了 你也少喝点 你待会儿还要上班的
- Takes the edge off. - I heard you were retiring man.
- 多喝点就可以少上班了 - 我听说你打算退休了
- I remember when this unit meant everything to you. - Used to mean something to you too.
- 我还记得以前对你来说这个部门就是你的一切 - 对你来说不也很重要嘛
YEAH, It wasn't easy walking away. Trust me.
离开并不是件容易的事 相信我
Going a little too far, kicking some ass to get the bad guy.
走得有点太远了 为了抓坏人也干过不少错事
It's not like that anymore.
现在跟以前已经完全不同了
We crossed over, Danny.
我们越界了 Danny
I SHOULD've done it back then.
我之前就应该那么做的
Just like you. Drawn my line in the sand.
就像你一样 划出自己的底线
- You can do that now. - Why do you think I'm getting out?
- 你现在也可以这么做的 - 要不然你以为我为什么要退出?
You care about that kid Jesse, you'll get him out too.
你很关心那个叫Jesse的孩子 你应该把他也弄出去
Hey Yates, is there something going on?
Yates 是不是发生了什么事情?
Is there something happening between you and Russ?
你和Russ之间是不是发生了什么?
MEET US AT THE SPOT
(约定地点碰面)
It's Russell.
是Russell
I gotta go.
我得走了
Hold on, hold on. Just a second.
等等 等等 就一会儿
What's going on? Is there something I need to know?
怎么了? 你是不是想告诉我什么?
You keep an eye on Jesse, alright?
你看紧点Jesse 好嘛?
Jesse, what's happening?
Jesse 怎么了?
M3 Colts have a stash house. Russell got a tip.
M3 Colts有个藏毒点 Russell收到了线报
He wants to do a takedown now, before they catch wind and move the product.
他现在就要去把它一锅端了 要赶在他们听到风声 转移毒品之前
Alright you keep an eye on the drugs. I'll call Rebecca. You gimme that location.
好的 你盯紧那些毒品 我打给Rebecca 你把地址发给我
ALL RIGHT
好
Front door. We stay together on this one.
从前门进 这回大家一起行动
You two hang back, Yates and I will take the lead.
你们俩殿后 我和Yates带头
They're going in.
他们进去了
Yates, upstairs, let's go.
Yates 楼上 咱们走
Jesse, let's go! Come on.
Jesse 咱们走! 快点
- Get your head out of your ass. - Jesse's stalling, something's up.
- 别像缩头乌龟似的 - Jesse退却了 有事发生
Yates!
Yates!
Easy, easy.
放松 放松
What the hell is going on?
这是他妈的怎么回事?
He shot Yates.
他开枪打了Yates
Officer Borden. You need to come with me.
Borden警员 麻烦你跟我走一趟
I've got questions about what happened today.
关于今天发生的事 我有一些问题想要问你
We gotta get him out of there.
我们得把他弄出来
Stay in the car. I don't want to burn him.
待在车里 我不想暴露他
I've got this.
我来处理
I want Jesse protected.
我希望Jesse能够得到保护
- Tell me you'll take care of him. - Rebecca.
- 告诉我你会照顾他的 - Rebecca
If it gets out that he went undercover on cops, it will chase him for the rest of his career.
如果他被发现以卧底的身份追查其他的警察 那他这辈子都别想摆脱这件事了
- Who the hell do you think you're talking to? - Either he walks away from this unscathed,
- 你以为自己是在跟谁说话? - 要么让他毫发无损摆脱干系
or I will personally make sure that everyone on this force knows
否则我以个人的名义向你保证 每一个警察都会知道
that the reason Detective Yates died is because you wouldn't back me.
Yates探员之所以会死 是因为你不愿意支援我
You'll be going down for this, not me.
你会因此而下台 不是我
It's been forever. How do you think he's doing in there?
这也等得太久了 你觉得他在里面会表现如何?
We'll see. Here he comes now.
我们会知道的 他来了
I think Russell killed him.
我觉得是Russell杀了他
I think he shot Yates and planted the gun on that kid at the scene.
我觉得是他枪杀了Yates然后把枪塞到了 那个在现场的孩子手里
It was the way he was moving around in that room. It was the way he looked.
看他在屋子里行动的样子就知道了 看他的眼神就知道了
Did you tell them that?
你有告诉他们吗
No, I can't just accuse another cop.
没有 我不能就这样控诉另外一名警察
Jesse, look at me.
Jesse 看着我
You gotta be sure.
你必须得确信不疑
He did it. I'm sure.
是他干的 我确定
Yates wanted out. He was leaving the unit.
Yates想要退出 他想要离开这个部门
Russell thought he was gonna blow the whistle on them. I sure of it.
Russell觉得他会去告发他们 我确定是这样的
We'll retake Officer Calvert's statement immediately, and go from there.
我们会立刻给Calvert警员重新做笔录 然后从那里开始查
- You're going to be discreet, you're going to take his name out of this. - Come on, that's not going to happen.
- 你得小心行事 你得把他的名字拿掉 - 得了吧 这不可能
- He'll be crucified. - A cop has been accused of murdering another cop, Rebecca.
- 他会被钉死在十字架上的 - 一名警察被控谋杀另一名警察 Rebecca
There's no way this doesn't get ugly.
这事儿肯定会变得很难堪的
Staff Inspector Harrison...
Harrison督察...
Has no authority here, this is IA's investigation, Rebecca.
他无权插手此事 这是内务部的调查 Rebecca
Either Jesse saw it or he didn't. I want his statement.
Jesse要么看见了 要么没看见 我需要他的陈述
We need proof. I'm not putting Jesse out there on his own.
我们需要证据 我不会让Jesse一个人去承担这些
Alright, then we stay under. We get to Russell first, before he feels the heat.
好的 那我们继续调查 我们得先抓住Russell 在他感觉到不对劲之前
- Rebecca wants everybody in the briefing room. - She can wait.
- Rebecca让大家都去会议室 - 他可以等
Yates was a friend of mine. There's no way.
Yates是我的朋友 这不可能
Russell is capable of a lot of things, but not that.
Russell有能力做许多事 但不是这件事
- I know what I saw. - Then you saw wrong.
- 我知道我看见了什么 - 那你肯定是看错了
I'll tell her you're coming.
我会告诉她你马上来
Middle of a raid, gunshots, things get foggy.
在突袭的过程中 枪击之后 看东西会变得模糊
- It's hard to know what exactly you saw, Jesse. - Maybe you've got tunnel vision.
- 很难去分辨你看到的到底是什么 - 也许你自己有视野狭窄的问题
This is hard for you, I get that. But if Jesse's right, he needs backup.
这对你来说很难 我明白的 但是如果Jesse是对的 那他需要支援
He also needs proof. He's the one on the line here.
他还需要证据 他才是暴露在外面的那个人
Yates was about to retire from the unit. Russell was paranoid he was going to talk.
Yates想要从部门里退下来 Russell妄想着他可能会去告发
- Let's use that paranoia. - Could be our best way in.
- 咱们就利用那个妄想 - 也许是咱们的机会
Daniel, you know Russell the best. You tell us.
Daniel 你最了解Russell了 不如你来说说吧
Look, if this is true,
听着 如果这是真的
maybe Jesse can call him, tell him he wants out of the unit.
也许Jesse可以打给他 说他想要退出
We need to make Russell feel like he's losing control.
我们得让Russell觉得他正在失去控制权
He'll be worried what Jesse saw at the raid. He'll want to come see him.
他会担心Jesse在突袭中看到的事情 他会想来见他
Okay Jesse, you talk to him, you got to open up.
好的 Jesse 你跟他谈谈 尽量把话说开
Tell him you're freaking out about what you saw in the house. You got to get him to talk, alright?
告诉他你被在那间房子里所看到的事情吓坏了 你得让他说出来 明白吗
You okay?
你还好吗
Yeah. I'm good.
没事 我没事
Alright let's get to work.
好了 咱们开工吧
You nervous?
你觉得紧张?
Yeah.
是啊
Me too.
我也是
Let me hear the audio again.
咱们再试一次音频
Can you say something? Give us a level.
你能说点什么吗 让我们测一下效果
Russell, I've been thinking.
Russell 我一直在想
I've been thinking it over, and it's not for me.
我一直在翻来覆去地想 我觉得这个不适合我
That's good, we're good. We're ready.
很好 能听到 我们准备好了
Jesse... Yeah.
- Jesse... - 嗯
You' got this, okay? You can do it.
你能行的 知道吗 你能做到的
Heads up.
注意了
Okay Jesse, they're coming to the door.
好了 Jesse 他们到门口了
- You alone? - Yeah.
- 就你一个人? - 是啊
I know what happened was tough, alright?
我知道之前发生的事情对你来说不容易 好嘛?
But it doesn't mean you need to leave the unit.
但这不表示你就得撂挑子
I been thinking about SMASH, what you guys do.
我一直在想关于SMASH的事 在想你们做的事
- It's just not for me. - What we do?
- 我觉得真的不太适合我 - 我们所做的?
Pounds, what's that mean, "What we do"?
Pounds 那是什么意思 "我们做的事"?
Beats me. What's that mean, Slick?
难倒我了 那是什么意思 小白脸
So let me get this straight. NOW...
那我不如就开门见山了
You want to leave.
现在 你想要离开
- Look, Jesse, I can't let that happen. - Nope.
- 听着 Jesse 我不会同意的 - 没门儿
No can do, J-bird.
想也不要想 小朋友
Russell's too paranoid, he's not going to talk.
Russell在狂妄了 他是不会说的
If you do leave, we have no chance but to tell everyone the truth.
如果你要走 那我们就没有选择了 只能告诉大家真相
Truth?
真相?
Truth about you.
关于你的真相
See, we paid Andre a visit this morning.
你看 今早我们去拜访了一下Andre
Turns out he remembers this night pretty clearly.
结果发现他对那晚的事情记得一清二楚
Mostly you, you kicking in his front door,
绝大多数都是你干的 踢他家的大门
waving a gun in his face.
拿把枪在他面前晃悠
Yeah, he remembers that real clear.
是啊 他记的真真切切
I was just doing what you guys told me to do.
我只是做了你们让我做的事
I never told you to intimidate anyone.
我从来没有叫你去恐吓他人
Destroy his possessions. I didn't tell you that, did I?
或者毁坏他的财物 我没有跟你说过 对吗
That's heavy badge syndrome. You couldn't be controlled.
你那是超级英雄附体了 你无法控制自己
Russell was trying to give you a shot and you - you blew it.
Russell试过要给你一个机会 但是你搞砸了
Fact is, the whole time we worked with you,
事实是 在我们跟你一起共事的时间里
you were breaking into houses, planting drugs, falsifying reports.
你一直在私闯民宅 栽赃毒品 篡改报告
Total behaviour problem.
你的表现一塌糊涂
Now, kinda makes sense, given where you came from.
现在想想觉得也有一定的道理 考虑到你的出身和背景
Read your file, kid, you grew up in Southside.
我看过你的档案 孩子 在南方长大的
Just another lonely kid looking to belong, right? The only problem is you're nothing but trouble.
不过是个孤独的小孩想要寻求归属感 对吗 问题是 你自己本身就是个大问题
I sure hope you're tired of being a cop, Jesse.
我当然希望你对于当警察感到厌倦了 Jesse
Because you are done.
因为你完蛋了
WHAT's he talking about?
他这是什么意思?
Russell's not going to give us anything. He's going to try to destroy Jesse's credibility.
Russell不会交待任何事的 他打算要毁掉Jesse的名声
That'll never stand up.
- 这样他就永无出头之日了 - 真的?
What's he doing?
他在干什么?
Daniel. Daniel!
Daniel Daniel!
He's going inside.
他要进去了
What is he thinking?
他在想什么呢
I don't know.
我不知道
- What are you doing? - I trusted you. How could you do this?
- 你这是干嘛? - 我相信你 你怎么能这么做?
Let's get the hell out of here man, we gotta go.
咱们赶紧离开这儿 我们得离开
Danny. What the hell man?
Danny 你他妈的怎么回事?
You going to tell me what's going on?
你能不能告诉我发生什么事了?
Listen to me. Just trust me, we gotta get out of here.
听我的 相信我就行 我们得离开这儿
NO, No one goes anywhere until you tell me what's going on.
在你告诉我发生了什么事之前 谁也不许离开
Listen, I got a buddy, alright.
听着 我有个朋友 明白么
He's got his ear to the ground, and he gave me a call.
他的消息很灵通 他给我打了个电话
IA, the kid's on the job, he's working you.
内务部 给这孩子派了任务 他是来查你的
Look, I'm sorry, I screwed up.
听着 我很抱歉 我搞砸了
I would've never brought him near you, if I knew.
我要是早知道 绝对不会把他介绍给你的
Yo, Russell, what's up, you're making me nervous over here.
Russell 怎么回事 你都让我觉得紧张了
The kid's working us.
这孩子在查我们
Hey, come on man, calm down.
嗨 来吧 伙计 冷静
Check the place, it's wired.
搜搜这地方 肯定有监听
Where is it?
在哪儿?
I don't know.
我不知道
Russell.
Russell
You little bitch.
你个臭小子
RUSSELL, COME ON, MAN. RUSSELL, RELAX. RELAX,MAN
Russell 别冲动
- I'm screwed, Danny. - Okay.
- 我完蛋了 Danny - 知道
So, what if the kid saw you get a little out of line.
那么 就算这小子看到你有些事情做过头了又怎样
Everyone knows that's what we do, that's part of the job.
大家都知道我们就是这么干的 这是我们工作的一部分
- Russell, what are we doing man; we should get out of here. - Shut up and let me think!
- Russell 我们这是在干什么 我们应该离开这儿 - 闭嘴 让我想想!
I JUST... I JUST... I just need to think. I just need to think.
我需要想一想 我只是需要想想
You.
是你
You introduced this kid to me.
是你把这孩子介绍给我的
- YEAH, Russ, I came to find you, I came to make this go away. - How do I know you're not wired?
- Russ 我是来找你的 我是来帮你脱身的 - 我怎么知道你没有带监听?
Russ. Come on!
Russ 得了吧!
The Bardi crew. Eight years ago, you remember that?
Bardi帮 八年前 你还记得吗
That big takedown we did? Remember that guy that was mouthing off too much?
我们执行的那次大行动? 还记得那个不断口出狂言的家伙吗
Costa Sanchez. You beat him up pretty bad, Russ.
Costa Sanchez 你可是把他揍得不轻啊 Russ
He ended up dying in hospital later.
他最后死在了医院里
I didn't report that.
我没有报告那件事
I protected you.
我保护了你
We're recording this. Does he know that?
我们正在录音 他知道吗
- What the hell are you doing Daniel? - And if I was wearing a wire would I say all of this?
- 你他妈的这是在干什么 Daniel? - 如果我也带着监听 我会说这些吗
I'm just as guilty as you.
我跟你一样的有罪
Russ, come on we're brothers, man. I had your back then.
Russ 来吧 咱们是兄弟 我们曾经互相支持对方
Don't I have it now?
现在不再是了吗
But you gotta talk to me, you gotta tell me what's going on Russell.
但是你得跟我说实话 你得告诉我发生了什么 Russell
What did you do?
你做了什么?
RUSS, what the hell is going on?
Russ 这是怎么回事?
- I'm in a lot of debt man. - Money?
- 我欠了一大笔钱 老兄 - 因为钱?
So, you took some money you shouldn't have, man.
所以 你拿了不属于你的钱
What else? We all get tempted. What else?
还有什么? 我们都有禁不起诱惑的时候 还有什么?
Russell!This place is wired.
这地方有监听 Russell!
It doesn't matter, not anymore.
没关系了 再也无所谓了
He was going to squeal.
他打算去告密
He was going to hurt us. All of us.
他想要伤害我们 我们所有人
Daniel, I needed him gone.
Daniel 我需要他消失
- Russell! - Shut up!
- Russell! - 闭嘴!
Are you talking about Yates, Russell?
你说的是不是Yates Russell?
Russell, did you shoot Yates?
Russell 你是不是开枪杀了Yates?
He told me he wasn't gonna let it go.
他告诉我他不会就这么算了的
I had to, for us, didn't I?
我不得不这么做 为了大家 不是吗
Daniel, I am in so deep man.
Daniel 我陷得太深了
I shouldn't have protected you back then.
早知道这样我当年就不应该保护你的
I'm taking you in.
我要逮捕你
You think you're better than me, is that it?
你觉得你自己比我好 对不对?
You would have done the same thing. We are the same.
换了是你也会做同样的事情的 你我都一样
We're not the same.
我们不一样
Not now.
现在不一样了
Not ever.
再也不一样了
- What happened with Daniel? - Daniel was a rookie cop when he was with SMASH.
- Daniel怎么样了? - Daniel在SMASH时还是个新人
A kid too scared to go against the force.
一个孩子因为害怕得罪上头才这么做的
That was my argument, to the Chief Inspector.
我是这么替他申辩的 跟总督察
Okay.
好的
AND he bought it?
他听进去了吗
That could have gone a different way.
事情有可能走向完全不同的方向的
I could've been wrong.
我有可能是错的
You guys all followed me in,
你们这些人都选择了跟随我
and I could've been wrong.
而我可能是错的
Yeah, but you weren't.
是啊 但是你没错
Look, Rebecca, what you did today.
听着 Rebecca 今天你所做的
Taking on the brass. IA. You put your team first.
在高层面前有担当 内务部 你把你的团队放在了第一位
No other cop I know would have been able to do that.
我认识的警察里 只有你才能做到这样
No other cop,
没有哪个警察
would've had the strength.
会像你这般的强韧
Russell said this thing to me. About the streets, what we do...
Russell对我说 他说的街头上的那些事 我们所做的...
How we're fighting a war that we can never win.
我们的斗争方式是永远赢不了的
You think he's right?
你觉得他是对的?
So what's the point of all this, then?
那么做这些事情的意义又何在呢
The war's not out there, it's in here.
外面并没有斗争 里面有
Up to you how long you want to fight.
由你来选择愿意坚持斗争多久
Good job today.
今天干得不错
What's this, what are you guys doing?
这是什么 你们这是什么意思?
Buying my friend Terri a drink, thought you might want to join us?
请我的朋友Terri喝一杯 我想你可能会想加入我们的?
You okay?
你没事吧?
ALRIGHT, I'm going to get a... Yeah. YEAH, YEAH
- 好吧 我正打算... - 好
Hey, Coach.
嗨 教练
I think I can use that pep talk now.
我想现在是你给我打气的好时机了
You seemed to be doing fine on your own today.
你今天靠自己就已经完成得很不错了
But, if I was, I'd tell you, you don't owe him anything, Daniel.
但是 如果我是你的教练 我会告诉你 你不欠他任何东西 Daniel
- You know that, right? - Guy made me the cop I am today.
- 你知道的 对吗 - 我能有今天全靠的他
No. You made the cop that you are today.
不 你能有今天全靠的你自己
With a little help from us.
还有我们小小的帮助
- What? - Thanks, man.
啥?
No problem.
- 谢谢 伙计 - 没事儿
- Hey can I get a beer? - Sure.
- 嗨 我能喝个啤酒吗 - 当然
So. Do you want to talk about it now or later?
那么 你想现在谈谈 还是之后再说?
Later. Okay?
以后再说吧 行吗
I'm not going anywhere.
我就待在这儿 哪也不去
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入